欢迎来到餐厅的提款机剪彩仪式
Welcome to the diner ATM ribbon cutting ceremony!
大家知道他拿的是
Everyone knows he's holding
普通大小的剪刀吧
normal-sized scissors, right?
阿憨只是在兴奋餐厅里终于有东西
Han's just excited that there's something in the diner
跟他是一个高度的了
the same size as him.
阿憨 你这是在浪费时间
Han, this is just another waste of time,
就像当时你开这家餐厅一样
like when you opened the diner.
这台机器现在正式投入营业
This machine is now open for business!
你剪刀用完了给我
After you're done with those,
我的"神龙巢"需要做点杂枝修剪
I need to do a little manscaping on my love mound.
等你修剪完 可以直接把剪刀扔了
And after you're done with that, you can throw them away.
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
这黄带子是干嘛
What's that yellow tape?
又有人死了吗
Did someone die again?
苏菲 不是啦 餐厅有提款机了
No, Sophie, we got an ATM.
我们本来就有"ATM"了啊
I thought we already had an ATM.
"亚裔变性男"[同一缩写]
"Asian Transgender Male."
谢谢你承认我是个"男"的
Well, thank you for saying "male."
好吧 给姐让个道
Well, move outta the way!
本宫要从国库取点银子
This broad's gotta do some bankin'!
小心点用 你是第一个呢
Be careful, you're the very first.
我们知道你等着对女人说这句话有多久了
We know how long you've been waiting to say that to a woman.
好的
Okay.
没有迪克 条子 与多管闲事白人
No sign of Deke, the cops, or nosy white folk.
快来私闯他家吧
Let's break in.
我不明白
I don't understand
我们为啥要闯进你男人的垃圾箱里
why we're breaking into your boyfriend's dumpster.
但我更不懂你是怎么站着尿尿的
The only thing I understand less is how you pee standing up.
为啥 不然你怎么尿的
Why? How do you pee?
我要跟迪克分手嘛
I am breaking up with Deke,
所以现在就到了感情中
so now's the part of the relationship
那段闯进他家拿回我东西
where I sneak in his place and get my stuff out
免去当面说分手的阶段啦
to avoid telling him I'm breaking up with him.
所以你直接跳过了每部浪漫爱情喜剧
Well, you just cut an hour out of
一小时左右的剧情
every romantic comedy.
免礼平身
You're welcome.
他是我第一个有摇把的对象
This is the first guy I dated that has a crank.
其他的都只是吸食冰毒[摇把]
most of them just did crank.
所以计划是这样
Okay, so here's the plan.
我计划爬上垃圾箱
I'm gonna climb up on the garbage,
解开窗子 钻进垃圾箱
unsnap the windows, dive in the dumpster,
然后拿走他放桌上的钥匙
and grab his spare key on the counter.
生命对你来说是否就是一场
Do you look at life as just a game
"让卡洛琳再突破下限"的游戏
of "Set new lows for Caroline"?
为什么要我来做这些事啊
Why do I have to do it?
卡洛琳 我还在假释期呢
I'm on parole, Caroline.
我们是要闯进一个垃圾箱里
We're breaking into a dumpster.
这事想非法都难
I don't even think that's illegal.
如果是真犯罪 我就不会只是假释啦
I didn't either. That's why I'm on parole.
灯开关在右边 钥匙在左边
Light on the right, key on the left.
有次我们把钥匙忘在最爱的酒吧里时也这么干
We did this once after Deke left his keys at our favorite bar,
其实那也只是家让人随便喝的贩酒店
which is actually just a liquor store where they let you drink.
他们都当没看见
They turn a blind eye.
因为那店员是真瞎子
Well, the guy is blind.
迪克总能找到有意思的地方
Yeah, Deke always found cool places.
那你为什么还跟他分手啊
Then why are you breaking up with him?
他跟你是天生一对
He's perfect for you.
你们都觉得住在个罐头里是可以接受的
You both think living in a tuna can is an acceptable habitat.
他是土豪又如何啊
So what if he has money?
有钱人与普通人不住在同个现实里
People with money don't live in the same reality.
如果特朗普是个穷鬼 他能有那头"秀发"吗
You think Donald Trump would have that hair if he were poor?
来吧 赶紧拿上我的牙刷就开溜
Now, come on, let's get my toothbrush and scram.
你买了牙刷吗 你是真的喜欢他啊
You bought a toothbrush? Oh, you really liked him.
等等 那是你其中一只花园矮人吗
Wait, Max, is that one of your gnomes?
天啊 你之前就是要搬来同居了
Oh, my God, you were practically moving in!
而且还是你最爱的那只
and it's your favorite one,
"矮呀是小受"
Gnome-o-sexual!
才不是 他是我第二喜欢的
No, this is my second-favorite.
我最喜欢的是那只"矮呀别搞事"
My favorite is "Gnome more drama."
而没带他来是因为他很烦这些事
And he's not here because he don't want no more drama,
说实话 我也烦这些事
And frankly, neither do I.
来啦 我们走吧
Come on, let's go.
你一声令下 我巴不得立刻逃出垃圾箱
You don't have to ask me twice to get out of a dumpster.
这不是麦百万吗
If it isn't Max-a-million.
还是应该说"恨我百万的麦克斯"
Or should I say, "Max who hates my millions"?
你不是该在忙着占领华尔街 抗议有钱人吗
Shouldn't you be occupying Wall Street or something?
我就是来拿回我的牙刷
I am just here for my toothbrush,
不会打扰到你坐在你象牙垃圾殿中
and then I'll leave you in your ivory dumpster
无所事事 下下金蛋玩的时间
to sit around and fart diamonds.
所以千万别误会啊 阿土伯
So don't get the wrong idea, Uncle Pennybags.
我不是来当你的阿土婶的
I'm not here to be Aunt Pennybags.
麦克斯 谁是阿土伯
Max, who's Uncle Pennybags?
以前性骚扰过你的大叔吗
Is he one of the ones who touched you?
是大富翁游戏里的那个老头啦
He's the monopoly man.
你看 你们两个真是天造地设的一对
See? You guys are perfect for each other.
对啊 麦克斯
Yeah, Max.
我们就像是约翰与洋子的完美版
We're like a more awesome version of John and Yoko.
也就是... 只有约翰他自己
Meaning, like, just John.
就算我有个几百万又如何
Who cares if I got a few million dollars?
是几个亿
A hundred few million.
根据微软必应搜索结果 最少也有这么多
And that's on the low end, according to Bing.
迪克 我晚点再来坐坐
Well, I'll be by later, Deke.
走吧 卡洛琳
Come on, Caroline.
麦克斯 你才不会来呢
No, Max, you won't.
你来拿东西就是想跟我分手
You're taking your stuff 'cause you're breaking up with me
但是你个小孬孬
and you're too big a baby pants
不愿意直接跟我说分手
to tell me you're breaking up with me.
你说什么
What?
我才没有要跟你分手
I am not breaking up with you.
我来拿牙刷是因为
I just needed my toothbrush
我中午吃了廉价虾子
because I had dollar shrimp for lunch
现在还有些虾壳卡在牙缝里呢
and I still have some shells in my teeth.
今晚晚点我再来跟你滚床单
I will see you later tonight for sex
以及做其他有的没的
and various whatnots.
我没有要跟你分手
I am not breaking up with you.
刚才分手得好狠啊
That breakup was brutal!
麦克斯 我听说咱们的迪克是土豪啊
Yo, Max, I hear our boy Deke got major money.
我早该想到了
I shoulda known,
因为他给我的大麻那可真是特供级的货啊
'cause the weed he gave me was real quality.
而且不要钱
And free.
厄尔 金钱能改变人 我深有体会
Earl, money changes people. I know.
每当到了发救济食品券时 我妈就忘了我是谁
Every time the food stamps came, my mother was all, "Max who?"
在场的各位父老乡亲们
'ello, my good people!
今儿个算你们行大运了
You are quite fortunate today,
有大土豪来你们这儿下馆子
for a rich person has come to dine in your establishment!
卡洛琳 替我在麦克斯那片儿给我弄一桌
Caroline, I would like a tabletop in Max's section, please.
这会儿应该让她开开眼 见识见识
Because it's high time she met the person
我一直隐藏的真实身份
I've been pretending not to be.
现在不用遮着掩着 她蒙对了
The veil has been lifted. She was correct.
我就是大富翁游戏的老头
I am the monopoly man.
先生 这边有请
Right this way, sir.
超浮夸演技区 正好有空位
I believe I have a table here in the overacting section.
好吧 我不得不承认被你逗笑了
All right, I'll give it up. You got me laughing.
如果我们真的断绝关系了 我很想你的
And I would miss all this if we didn't hang out,
所以我们还是当朋友
So I guess we can still be friends
和烘焙学校搭档吧
and pastry school partners.
什么烘焙学校搭档
Pastry school partners?
我都把你的咪咪加进我遗嘱里了
Your breasts are named in my will.
不是吧 你不会是真的要跟我分手吧
Come on, you can't be serious about this.
别担心 我们还是可以一起做
Don't worry, we can still do all the stuff
我们计划好未来要做的事啊
we had planned for our future.
比如14号那天把阿憨家挂满卷纸
Like tping Han's apartment on the 14th--
我可不会翻脸不认人
I'm not a monster.
-麦克斯 -迪克 你不能当我的男朋友
- Max... - Deke, you can't be my boyfriend.
现在起 我就是穷人救济金
From now on I'm like welfare.
你得是穷人才能拥有
You have to be broke to get some.
麦克斯 我真心希望你重新考虑
Max, I really wish you'd reconsider
跟迪克分手的事
breaking up with Deke.
你们俩真的很合得来
I mean, you guys get along great.
他住在垃圾箱里
He lives in a trash can,
也跟你一样喜爱尿尿笑话
he shares your love of pee-pee jokes.
他的头发能藏东西
He can hide things in his hair.
在知道他是有钱人之前
Aren't those the things you didn't like about him
这不都是你讨厌的点吗
before you knew he had money?
是啊 但人是可以改变的
Yes, but people can change.
改变自己 喜欢他吧
So change and like him.
别这样嘛 至少保持开明的态度
Come on, just keep an open mind.
你何不现在就上床去想想呢
In fact, why don't you sleep on it?
现在去 去吧 上床去
Right now. Go. Go to bed.
去去去去去
Go, go, go, go, go.
天啊 你就这么着急要自慰
Boy, are you eager to masturbate.
你好啊 伙伴
Hey, friend.
来吧 快上床来
Come on, get in.
-我都跟你说我不能再看见它了 -为什么
- I told you I can't see that anymore. - Why?
你是我的伙伴 他也是我的小伙伴
You're my friend, he's my friend.
我们都是伙伴而已嘛
We're all just friends.
你怎么会有我家钥匙
Where did you get a key?
别生气 我请她帮忙了
Don't be mad. I asked her for help.
卡洛琳 快滚进来
Caroline, get in here!
不行 我在自慰呢
Can't. I'm masturbating!
卡洛琳 你在干嘛
Caroline, what are you doing?
那些是新鞋子吗
Are those new shoes?
是的
Uh, yes.
它们从哪来的
Where did they come from?
一回家就在这了
They were just here.
刚好合你的脚吗
In your size?
这是神迹啊
It's a miracle.
是我送的
They're from me.
我买给她的礼物
I got 'em for her as a gift.
你凭啥觉得你能收买我的室友
What makes you think you could buy my roommate?
她说"你给我买新鞋我就给你钥匙"
She said, "I'll give you the key if you buy me new shoes."
是为了爱情
For love!
我是为了爱情啊
I did it for love!
你们俩应该在一起
You two belong together.
就像我跟小鞋鞋一样
Like me and these shoes.
别这样 求你给我一次机会
Come on, just give me a chance to express
告诉你我内心深处的感受
my deep feelings about this.
麦克斯 我想说...
Max, what I'm trying to say is...
我不想当你的朋友
I don't wanna be your friend.
我想当你的男朋友
I wanna be your boyfriend.
你现在看起来像要当我的女朋友
Well, right now it looks like you want to be my girlfriend.
我给你指点迷津一下吧
Maybe I can help clear things up.
这又得花我多少银子
How much is this gonna cost me?
分文不收好吗
Nothing. Look...
麦克斯觉得自己不应该拥有个有钱人
Max doesn't think she deserves someone rich
因为她...
because she has...
-自尊心超低 -错了
- Well, low self-esteem. - Wrong.
姐没有自尊
I have no self-esteem.
还有 我现在能看到你的蛋蛋底
And I can see the bottom of your balls.
麦克斯 还记得两天前
Max, remember two days ago
你曾是个爱我蛋蛋底的姑娘吗
when you loved the bottom of my balls?
那时候以为它们很穷 我心疼它们
That's when they were poor and I felt sorry for them.
何苦呢 你们是天生一对
Come on, you two belong together.
像是蛋蛋笑话界里的罗密欧与朱丽叶
You're like the Romeo and Juliet of ball banter.
抱歉 但这就是不行
I'm sorry, it's just never gonna work.
我们就像是两个不同宗教家庭长大的 像...
It's like we were raised with different religions, like...
宗教有哪些啊
What are two religions?
你是想要观众给点意见呢
Are you taking suggestions from the audience,
还是你真不知道两个任意宗教的名字
or do you really not know the names of two religions?
比如说
Let's say...
一个女巫与一个蓝精灵
a witch and a smurf.
你的问题有答案了
Question answered.
比如我是个女巫 而你是个蓝精灵
So it's like I'm a witch and you're a smurf.
大家都知道我们是不可能在一起的
We could never be together. Everybody knows that.
我一辈子都当个女巫 没当过蓝精灵
I've only lived like a witch. I've never lived like a smurf.
所以我完全不懂你
So I don't get you.
又蓝又软弱是什么感觉啊
What's it like being blue and soft?
我不知道 我是个女巫 我又绿又强大
I don't know, I'm a witch. I'm green and all-powerful.
所以你是说 咱俩不是同一个世界的人
So you're saying you can't relate to me
因为你从没当过蓝精灵吗
because you've never been a smurf?
哇 五雷轰顶啊
Wow. That's heavy.
好吧 我该走了
Well, I'm gonna go.
我最好脱下这傻袍子 换回我的短裙再走
Oh, I better take off this silly robe and put on my skirt.
她也得把鞋子还回去
And she's giving back the shoes.
别想 她才不会还
Oh, no, she is not!
"语种选择
"Language preference:
英语 西班牙语 中文 法语"
English, Spanish, Chinese, French."
这玩意应该根据餐厅人群来定制语种
They should've made this more specific to the diner.
"嬉皮士 流浪汉 瘾君子 少女孕妇"
"Hipster, hobo, junkie, pregnant teen."
别忘了还有"撞伤头的芭蕾舞女"
Don't forget "Ballerina with a head wound."
"您是否要查看账户余额"
"Would you like to see your account balance?"
那台提款机就是一贱人
That ATM's a real bitch.
我有个17岁的辣妹[17块钱] 想[取]出来
Yeah, I got a hot 17 in here that's dying to get out.
之前奥列格也这么说 后来被警察拦了下来
So did Oleg when that cop pulled him over.
卡洛琳 瞧瞧这收据
Caroline, look at this receipt.
肯定是出错了
This can't be right.
上次同事见到这么多零
I haven't seen this many zeros in one place
还是在餐厅的圣诞派对上呢
since the diner Christmas party.
上面显示你有100万零17块
That says $1,000,017.
阿憨 你的提款机坏了
Han, your ATM's broken.
它刚让麦克斯的账户多了100万
It just gave Max $1 million.
闪开 闪开 闪开
Out of my way! Out of my way! Out of my way!
我终于等到了 提款机出错乱给人钱
This is it--the faulty ATM that gives out millions.
我以为这跟尖锐湿疣一样 只是坊间传闻而已
I thought it was an urban legend like HPV.
大家别动
Everybody freeze.
那破玩意肯定是坏掉了
The damn thing must be busted.
为了搞这台提款机 我腰都要累弯了
And to think I bent over backwards to get that ATM.
我也曾为了西语能得B "弯下腰"求老师
Well, I bent over forwards to get a "B" in Spanish.
靠 我的账户还跟以前一样
Damn it. My account's exactly the same.
冻结中
Frozen.
对了 迪克之前有留张条给你
So, Deke left this note for you earlier.
我都120岁了 能想起来就不错了
I forgot 'cause I'm 120.
现在你知道当蓝精灵是什么感觉了
Now you know what it's like to be a smurf.
说出来都没人信 那100万是迪克给我的
Can you believe this? Deke gave me $1 million!
所以那是真的钱吗
So that's real money?
那钱是真的吗
The money's real?
你有100万
You have $1 million?
我们成了百万富翁了
We're a millionaire?
早上好 我的朋友
Oh, good morning, my good man.
我最近突然得到一笔钱
I recently came into some money,
所以给自己买了个糖果皇冠
thus the candy tiara.
我想跟大家分享我的财富
And I wanted to spread the wealth.
给
Here.
这罐咖啡送你
Have a pound of coffee.
福爵牌的哦 因为我现在是百万富翁啦
It's Folgers, since I'm a millionaire now.
这是"一觉醒来变有钱人"最爽的部分
Best part of waking up rich!
我为所有的好朋友们都准备了礼物
I come bearing gifts for all my best friends.
站在我身后的男人 给
Here, guy who stands behind me...
给你一盒12节的7号电池
A 12-pack of triple-a batteries for you.
没错 便利店的人专门为我打开玻璃橱
And yes, they did have to open the glass case at CVS
我才能拿来送你
for me to get these.
站在我旁边的女人 给
Here, lady on the other side.
洗发水和护发素
A shampoo and conditioner!
伊卡璐的 不值几个钱啦
Herbal Essences, no big deal.
我不会忘了你那份的 怪发妹
And don't think I forgot about you, peek-a-boo hair.
送你一盒高迪瓦的巧克力
A Godiva box of chocolates.
你不是在做梦 这真的是高级巧克力哟
No, you're not dreaming. I said "Godiva"!
麦克斯 我有个好消息
Max, I have great news.
还有你 为了一双鞋子出卖我的女人
And you, woman who sold me out for shoes.
我出去扫货的时候
I got you something very special
为你挑了一份特别的礼物
when I was out gift shopping.
你还记得你经常说
You know how you always say,
"我要跟哪个学员搞 才能搞到一个食品封口夹"
"Who do I have to bang to get a chip clip around here?"
答案就是我
Me!
什么 你花那笔钱了吗
Wait, you spent money?
我们那100万 你花了多少
How much of our million did you spend on your...
在你这次"疯狂购物"上
we'll call it a shopping spree.
差不多全花掉了
Almost all of it.
看来公立学校连花钱都没教好
Okay, our public schools have failed you.
但你没去上过 它们想没教好你都没机会
Or they would have if you'd went.
但我现在太兴奋 顾不上这个了
But I'm too excited to care.
先说重要的 我们什么时候辞掉餐厅的工作
First things first. When do we quit the diner?
你在瞎说什么 我们才不会辞职
What are you talking about? We're not quitting the diner.
我要把剩下的钱还给他
I'm giving the rest of the money back.
等下等下 这念头就此打住
Hold on, hold on, pump the brakes.
有什么问题吗 你已经得到你想要的封口夹了
What's the problem? You got a chip clip--you're set.
我花钱是为了向迪克表明我的态度
I only spent it to make a point to Deke.
你不能还回去 我已经计划好了 大计划
You can't give it back. I have plans. Big plans.
我们先辞掉餐厅的工作
After we quit the diner,
然后我认识个人 他可以把这小100万翻三倍
I found a guy who can turn that measly million into 3.
别担心 他的名字不在
And don't worry, he was not named
我爸庞氏骗局的涉案人员名单中
in my father's Ponzi Scheme.
至少他现在这个假名不在
Well, not by the name he goes by now.
你好啊 蓝妹妹
What up, smurfette?
你好 迪克
Oh, hello, Deke.
你刚错过了我用你这100万
You just missed me passing out
给大家发礼物的豪气场面
all the gifts I bought with your million,
但你正好及时赶到 可以见证
But you're here in time to see me
我收买大玛丽当我搭档这一刻
buy Big Mary as my lab partner.
抱歉 我是非卖品
Who says I'm for sale?
猛男消防员日历
A fireman's calendar...
再加壮汉消防员日历
and another fireman's calendar.
成交
Sold.
我猜你肯定没想到我会花这笔钱吧
I bet you didn't think I'd spend that money, hmm?
那你就大错特错了
Well, you were wrong.
我花了整整143块
I spent $143!
麦克斯 我就是想让你花这笔钱
Max, I wanted you to spend the money
好让你知道当有钱人是什么感觉
so you know what it's like to be rich.
现在我们都是蓝精灵了
Now we're both smurfs.
我们有是同一世界的人了
You can relate to me again.
想像上周二那样 去烤箱那
Wanna go do hand stuff by the ovens
干点"手工活"吗
like we did last Tuesday?
所以你是想用这笔钱收买我吗
Oh, so you were just trying to buy me with the money?
我不是那种高价的应招女郎
Well, I'm not a high-priced call girl.
因为超级碗的欢乐周末已经结束了
'cause Super Bowl weekend's over.
给 剩下的钱还给你
Here. I'm giving you the rest of the money back.
别冲动
Okay...
她现在精神状态明显不能够
Obviously, she is not mentally competent enough
正确地处理她的财务
to handle her finances.
就像当时我奶奶
This is like when my grandma
想把她所有的钱都捐给一个孤儿院
wanted to give all her money to that orphanage,
所以我们不得不对外说她有老年痴呆症
so they had her diagnosed with Alzheimer's.
还你
Here.
真不敢相信我会有一个
I can't believe I'm losing all of my money
两次失去所有钱的人生
twice in one lifetime.
谁有哮喘吸入器
who has an inhaler?
注意看 我还把你的名字写上了
And check it. I even put your name on there.
"超级有钱一辈子无需为五斗米折腰的迪克"
"Deke Mc-Richy Mc-Never-Had-Yo-Work-For-Anything"?
抱歉 我还应该写上
Oh, sorry, I probably should've added,
"爱装穷人的有钱佬"
"Richy Rich Pretended-He-Was-Poor-instein"
好让人们知道那是你
So they'd know it's you.
来 我改一下
Here, I'll fix it.
没错 我也赏了自己好东西
Oh, yes. I treat myself well.
麦克斯 别闹了
You know what, Max? Stop.
我竭尽全力向你证明
I've tried everything to show you
我不是卡通里的那种土大款
I'm not some cartoon rich guy,
可你还是认为我是个笑话
and you still think I'm a joke.
你眼里只看到了我有钱 但我不止如此
You only see me as my money, but I'm not.
这就是金钱对我的意义
That's how much money means to me.
但你说得对
But you were right.
咱俩的确不合适
It's not gonna work with us.
麦克斯 我收到你的礼物了
Max. Oh, I got your gift.
我超爱我新的电动棒
I love my new vibrator.
那不是电动棒 苏菲
It's not a vibrator, Sophie.
那是吸尘器
It's a Dustbuster.
好吧 现在我"那里"也一尘不染了
Well, there's no dust there anymore.
我去我卡座坐着啊
I'll be in my booth.
小二 小二
Waitress. Waitress.
"小二" 她在喊谁呢
"Waitress"? Who's she talking to?
小姐
Miss...
我的三文鱼吃起来像鸡肉
This salmon tastes like chicken.
那就奇怪了 因为那是猪肉做的
That's weird, 'cause it's pork.
就个小二跟我耍什么脾气
I don't need attitude from some waitress.
你一直喊的小二到底是谁啊
Who is this waitress you keep referring to?
你的工作是帮我点餐
Your job is to take my order,
对我笑脸相向 然后好好服务我
put a smile on your face, and serve me.
当然不是
Oh, hell, no!
老娘才不用受你的气
I don't have to take this.
我给你看样东西 肥婆
Let me show you something, doll.
这是我上次用提款机时打的余额单
This is my receipt from the last time I used the ATM.
你看见最后一行的"账户余额"有多少吗
You see where it says "Account balance" at the bottom there?
麻烦念给我听 谢谢
Read that number to me, please.
如果你有100万 你干嘛还在这里工作
If you have $1 million, why would you be working here?
问得好
Good question.
你好像很暴躁 要用我的吸尘器治疗"积怨"吗
You seem cranky. You want to use my Dustbuster?
那女人刚才问我
That woman just asked me
如果我有100万 我干嘛还在这里工作
if I have $1 million, why am I working here?
我之前不就说了嘛
That's what I've been saying.
我是说 我有100万耶
I mean, I have $1 million.
我之前不就说了嘛
That's what I've been saying.
老娘不用在这垃圾地方上班
I don't need to be in this dump!
重申一遍 我之前不就...
Again, that's what I've--
你是说了 我知道 我是个白痴
You've been saying! I know, I'm an idiot!
钱我决定不还给他了
I'm keeping that money!
我之前不就说了嘛 不能还啊
That's what I've been saying!
-麦克斯 卡洛琳 -闭嘴
- Max, Caroline-- - No.
你都不知道我要说什么呢
You don't even know what I was about to say.
不管是什么 都给老娘闭嘴
Whatever it is, no.
我们有100万
We have $1 million.
是的 我们有100万
Yeah, we have $1 million.
没错 我们有100万 老娘不干了
Yeah, we have $1 million, and I quit!
老娘也不干了 小宝贝
And I quit too, baby!
我从上班第一天就恨这个破地方
I have hated this hellhole from day one.
再见[日文] 小矮子
Sayonara, short stuff!
我不知道哪个词更过分
I don't know what's more offensive.
是被当做"小日本" 还是"小矮子"
"Sayonara" or "short stuff"!
我觉得是"小日本"比较狠 小矮子
I would go with "Sayonara," short stuff.
这脱衣速度比12岁的小毛孩
That got off quicker than
看见梅根·福克斯的"缴械"速度还快
a 12-year-old looking at Megan Fox.
快吗
Quick?
三年以来 我一直梦想着脱掉这身制服
I've been trying to get out of this thing for three years.
拉链卡住了 这就像部恐怖片
This zipper is stuck! This is like a horror movie!
帮我 快帮我把这死玩意脱下来
Help me! Get this damn thing off me!
扯下来 剪烂 再一把火烧了它
Tear it off, cut it off, light it on fire!
但小心我的头发
Well, watch my hair.
无所谓了 反正我有钱可以买新头发
Oh, who cares! I'll buy new hair!
靠 我从上面脱吧
Damn it, I'll just go over.
太棒了 我们解脱了
Yes! We're out of here.
再也不用想着餐馆和小蛋糕店了
No more diner, no more cupcakes.
慢着 连小蛋糕店也不要了吗
Wait, wait, no more cupcakes?
你在说什么啊
What are you talking about?
我们可以用这笔钱扶植我们的事业
With all this money, we can grow our business.
我什么都不要扶植
Oh, I'm not growing anything
除了我床头柜那株超级大麻
except a big-ass weed plant on my nightstand.
但那是我们的梦想
But it's our dream.
我不需要梦想 穷人才需要梦想活下去
I don't need a dream. Dreams are for poor people!
老娘有100万
I have $1 million.
我不要去上烘焙学校了
I'm not going to pastry school,
我甚至连厕所都不用去上了
I might not even go to the bathroom.
我余生要死赖在床上不下来了
And I am definitely not getting out of bed.
我以后什么事都不用干
I will never do anything again!
天啊 我以后什么事都不干了
Oh, my god, I'll never do anything again.
我们不能辞职
We're not quitting.
我就知道
I knew it!
拜你和这拉链所赐 我永远也摆脱不掉这身制服
Between you and this zipper, I'll never get outta here.
我不行 你也听见我有100万后会变啥样
I can't. You heard what I'd be like with $1 million.
我肯定30岁就死了
I'd be dead at 30.
但这不是你一直以来的愿望吗
But isn't that what you've always wanted?
阿土伯 你在家吗
Hey, Uncle Pennybags, you home?
我是说 你在垃圾箱吗
I mean, you dumpster?
我能进去吗
Hey, can I come in?
还是你已经放下了
Or did you already move on?
-如果是我也能理解 -没 进来吧
- 'cause I'd get it if you did. - Nah, come in.
我无所事事 下下金蛋玩呢
Just sittin' in here fartin' diamonds.
我觉得我欠你一个道歉
Look, I think I owe you an apology.
之前我称你为"住在象牙垃圾殿里
You know how I called you a lazy mc-richy rich who never
超级有钱一辈子无需为五斗米折腰的懒蛋"
had to work for anything and lives in an ivory dumpster?
这是道歉的一部分吗
Is this part of the apology
还是你在重述你伤我的心的过分句子
Or just the recap of mean things you've said to me?
乖乖听着
Just listen.
我说得对 你的确无需为五斗米折腰
Well, I was right, you never did have to work for anything.
我开始怀疑你到底懂不懂什么是道歉了
Okay, I'm starting to think you don't know what an apology is.
但即使你天生无需为五斗米折腰
But even though you never had to work for anything,
但你却付出努力
You do.
你真的有乖乖起床 好好上烘焙学校
You actually get up, you go to pastry school,
还盖了一个垃圾箱房子 你努力做了很多事
and you build dumpsters, you do lots of stuff.
你还不知道我搞的慈善事业呢
Hey, you're not even familiar with my charity:
"为老人谋高潮"机构
Orgasms for old people.
这最好不是你开玩笑的
I hope you're not joking.
真相是 我不能忽略你的钱
Look, the truth is I couldn't see past your money.
但我只当你是个蓝精灵
All I saw was smurf.
我之前认为女巫和蓝精灵不能在一起
And I thought witches and smurfs couldn't be together,
我错了
but I was wrong.
没错
Yeah, you were.
麦克斯 你把钱要回来了吗
Max, did you get back the check yet?
因为我刚找到另一位投资人
Because I just found a different investment guy.
德国的合法投资人
A legit one in Germany.
他名叫赫尔·斯路芬
His name is Herr Schluffen.
抱歉 我现在就要把钱还回去
Well, I'm sorry. I'm giving it back right now.
赫尔·斯路芬可以去死橹粪了
Herr Schluffen can schluff off.
等下 麦克斯 我能握一下这100万吗
Wait, Max, can I hold the million?
一秒就好 让我重温上层中产阶级的感觉
For just one more second, I want to be upper-middle class.
卡洛琳 把钱还回去
Caroline, give it back.